facerig.com 2017-06-06

# FaceRig

According to the provisions of Romanian law no. 677/2001 regarding individual protection for personal data processing and sharing of said data, modified and revised and Romanian Law no. 506/2004 regarding processing personal data and protection of privacy in regard to electronic communication, Holotech Studios SRL, situated at Emanoil Porumbaru 77, 4’th floor, Sector 1 Bucharest, Romania (as a private data operator) is obligated to securely manage the personal data provided by you ( **„Personal Data”** ) and use it only for the purposes specified below.

The purpose of collecting Personal Data is enabling the use of the facerig.com website and forum and/or enabling the Social Media Sharing module present in the FaceRig software suite.

In this context we mention that Holotech Studios SRL and its legal sub-contractors managing the FaceRig.com web page can process the following types of Personal Data: (i) your e-mail address, (ii) multimedia content created by you (screenshots, video or audio feeds) containing Personal Data (iii) content posted by you on the FaceRig.com forum (containing Personal Data).

You are not required to provide the Personal Data, this data is only necessary for (i) Using the Facerig.com discussion forum (in the case of your e-mail address) and (ii) the „Social Media Sharing” functionality pf the FaceRig Software Suite ( in the case of using the Frig Media Uploader Facebook app to post images, video or audio created by you with the FaceRig Software Suite to your Facebook account via our web server, where the above mentioned video and audio content will be temporarily stored for a few hours before being automatically deleted). Furthermore we no not require other Personal Data thus we encourage you to be careful when using Personal Data in your forum posts, as all the data you post to the Facerig.com forum will be stored on our servers and will be accessible to facerig.com visitors.

By finalizing the forum registration process you acknowledge and confirm that you want to use the FaceRig.com forum and therefore you agree to the processing of your Personal Data as mentioned above.

Your refusal implies the impossibility of using the FaceRig.com forum and the impossibility of using the „Social Media Sharing” module from the FaceRig Software Suite.

The facerig.com webpage and the media upload functionality of the „Social Media Sharing” module from the FaceRig Software suite are hosted on the high speed webserver located in Germany. Therefore, the Personal Data may be transferred in Germany.

If you no longer wish to use these services please contact us at so that your Personal Data may be erased from our databases.

The facerig.com website uses both session ID cookies and persistent cookies as part of its interaction with your browser. A cookie is an alphanumeric identifier (a file) that web sites transfer to your computer’s hard drive through a web browser to enable its systems to recognize your browser for record-keeping purposes. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser, while a persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time.

The facerig.com website uses Google Analytics and Google Adwords, an ad tracking and delivery technology that is provided by Google. We store Adwords cookies for remarketing purposes on your browser in order to later serve you ads about FaceRig. This is collected anonymously and no information to connect it with your account, email or name is stored .For more information about Google Analytics and Google AdWords , please visit [https://www.google.com/analytics/](https://www.google.com/analytics) and [http://www.google.com/adwords/](http://www.google.com/adwords)

The facerig.com website uses Twitter Ads, an ad tracking and delivery technology that is provided by Twitter. We store Twitter Ads cookies for remarketing purposes on your browser in order to later serve you ads about FaceRig. This is collected anonymously and no personal information is stored within them. For more information about Twitter Ads policies, please visit [Twitter.com Policies](https://support.twitter.com/articles/20171365?lang=en). Twitter supports Do Not Track (DNT). When you have DNT enabled in your browser, Twitter does not match your account to browser-related information to tailor ads for you.  
By configuring the options in your browser, you may control how cookies are processed by your system. However, if you decline the use of cookies you may not be able to use certain features on this site.

According to law no. 677/2001 you have the right to access and intervene on the data, you have the right not to be subjected to an individual decision and the right to address a court of law. At the same time, you have the right to oppose the processing of your Personal Data and to request its deletion.

To make use of the above mentioned rights, you may address a written request, complete with a date and signature,to Holotech Studios SRL info@facerig.com
